# Liyu (Jade) Lin

https://llyu0966.github.io/portfolio/

lliyu.brooklyn@gmail.com • (347)-277-9945 • https://github.com/llyu0966 • https://www.linkedin.com/in/liyu-lin/ • https://llyu0966.github.io/myblog/

# **Objective**

Adaptable Computer Science major (3.8/4.0 GPA) currently attending Brooklyn College. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of programming, research & analysis skills, and web design to successfully fill the Programmer Intern at a technology company. Frequently praised as diligent by my peers.

#### **Technical Skills**

• Java: 3 year • HTML/CSS: 3 year • JavaScript: 2 year

• UNIX/Linux: 2 year • C++: 1 year • R: 1 year

• H2 Database: 1 year 
• Python: 1 year 
• ReactJS: beginner

### **Education**

#### BS, Computer Science, Mathematics Minor, Brooklyn College/CUNY

Expected Graduation Date: Dec 2021

- GPA: 3.86/4.00.
- Relevant courses: Data Structure, Computer Architecture, Math Modeling & Simulation, Human-Computer Interaction, Numerical Analysis, Database Systems.
- Received Dean's List Awards (2018 Fall, 2019 Fall, 2020 Spring, 2020 Fall).
- Member of Upsilon Pi Epsilon computing discipline honor society.

#### AS, Accounting, ASA College.

Jun 2017

- GPA: 3.88/4.00.
- Relevant courses: Advanced Bookkeeping, Computerized Accounting, Principles of Finance, Principles of Microeconomics, Accounting with Electronic Spreadsheet.
- Certificate of Completion of the Courses in Mastering Inventory, Mastering Payroll, Mastering Adjusting Entries, Mastering Depreciation, Mastering Correction of Accounting Errors from The American Institute of Professional Bookkeepers.
- Member of Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society.

### **Experiences**

### EasyFind Co. Arcadia, California

Sep 2020 - Dec 2020

#### **Web Developer**

• Intern at a comprehensive information service platform that provides membership to international students in the United States. Playing a role of backend design and website maintenance.

# Berk Trade and Business School, Long Island City, NY Assistant to Office Manager

May 2018 - Aug 2018

- Filed and retrieved corporate documents, records, and reports.
- Answered phone calls and direct calls to appropriate parties or took messages.
- Performed general office duties, such as performing basic bookkeeping work.

# Adier Corporation, Long Island City, NY Web Developer

Aug 2017 - May 2018

- Designed, built, and maintained web sites which reached 100% customer satisfaction, according to customer survey, using authoring or scripting languages, content creation tools, and digital media.
- Created reports for the Management to track the keyword rankings for web sites, using Google Analytics, SERP tools, or Moz.

# United Reliance Group Inc. New York, NY Bookkeeper Intern

Feb 2017 - May 2017

- Implemented the QuickBooks software to record, store, and analyze information.
- Received checks and vouchers, recorded them into debit or credit accounts, and examined the records for the bank

## **Extracurricular & Academic Activities**

JPMorgan Chase & Co. On-line
Software Engineering Virtual Experience Program Participant

Jun 2020 - One Week

Participated in the open access JPMorgan Chase & Co. Virtual Experience Program with InsideSherpa.

#### Tasks Completed include:

- Using a stock price data feed and set up system for analysis the financial data to enable traders to identify when trading for the stock should occur.
- Implement the Perspective (JPMorgan Software) open source code for data visualization.
- Use Perspective to create the chart for the trader's dashboard.